Franco Miguel E. Dosdos

333-13A M. Paez St, Brgy. Punta Princessa, Cebu City

Birthdate: October 24, 2000 Contact number: 09667649415

School Email: francomiquel.dosdos@cit.edu

Email: francodosdos@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To establish a secure position within my field and expand knowledge that will develop and challenge the skills I have acquired throughout my education and



passions. To perform the necessary and required objectives in the company and to reach the desired goals with competence and creativity with life-long learning and experience in mind. I believe I can offer the knowledge and skills required in the company and to continually grow as an employee.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Knowledge in various Programming Languages such as C, JAVA, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, Python and GDScript.
- Knowledge in music theory and arrangement.
- Knowledge in sound design, mixing, and mastering and recording live music.
- Proficiency in the use of popular DAW(Digital Audio Workstations) FL Studio, Audacity, wWise, and Ableton Live Suite.
- Proficiency in the use of editing software Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe Photoshop and the like.

EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS

- Fluent in English oral and written communication
- Proficiency in Conversational Japanese
- Team-oriented
- Technology and Media Literate
- Passion for excellence and creativity
- Quality Control
- Problem Solving

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

- July 2014 until 2017 Science & Tech writer for Campus Journalism Ignis
- March 2014 until 2017 School Audio Tech
- January 2016 to Present Producer & Mixing Engineer for
- April 2020 to January 2021 Graphic Designer for Pen Chemistry

EDUCATION

 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Cebu Institute of Technology - University Natalio B. Bacalso Ave, Cebu City (2019-2023) Graduated Year: 2023

REFERENCES

- Mr. Junnel Dayanan
 Music Teacher, Junior High School
 Matilda L. Bradford Christian School
 Contact no. 0999 867 7883
- Ms. Jessacristi Maria Abella Teacher, Junior High School Matilda L. Bradford Christian School Contact no. 0999 317 1621
- Ms. Beatrice Mae Garcia Journalist, Ignis Cebu, Philippines Contact no. 0995 625 3776